

Stefan Zafirovski, UI/UX Designer

Dedicated UI/UX designer with background and education in multiple design disciplines. Extremely focused on continuous education and research in the field, to provide the most effective solutions to any challenge at hand.

After almost 10 years of managing a business in my home country - North Macedonia, and finishing a UI/UX Academy, I moved to Prague, looking for new challenges and opportunities.

Employment History

Graphic designer & Manager at Prizma Promet, North Macedonia

May 2013 — Present

- Worked to achieve high customer satisfaction rates by providing optimal and creative design solutions for any type of printed brand materials: business cards, brochures, large-scale prints, vehicle advertising, etc.
- Followed existing brand guidelines, or worked towards establishing new ones when needed.
- Helped to increase customer return rates by providing excellent customer service at all times.
- Managed company processes and operations.

Freelance Graphic Designer at upwork.com (odesk) & fiverr.com

June 2009 — August 2014

 Provided digital design solutions for a range of clients from different industries, while maintaining continuous excellent customer ratings.

Education

UI/UX design, Brainster academy

March 2021 — March 2022

Finished a year-long UI/UX academy with 14 modules, covering all areas of UI/UX design, including:

- Design Thinking
- Research methods
- Wireframing
- Prototyping tools (Adobe XD, Figma, Invision, Framer), etc.

Apart from establishing a good theory background, as part of the learning process, we worked on projects for real clients.

I was selected as a Student of the month for the UI/UX academy in July 2021:

https://blog.brainster.co/dream-team-juli/

UI/UX Design, Semos education

October 2018 — February 2019

Successfully finished a UI/UX academy with a focus on:

- Design principles
- · Web animations
- SEO

After finishing the academy, I got certified as Adobe Certified Associate in Adobe Animate.

MSc of Science in Project Management, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Information Technologies, Skopje, North Macedonia

September 2014 — May 2018

Successfully finished my master's degree program and worked on my master's thesis "UI Design Optimization and Analysis on Coupon Platforms for Improving Service Quality".

The thesis was based on in-depth research on one of the biggest coupon platforms in North Macedonia: grouper.mk.

BSc in Economics in E-business, Faculty of Economics - E-business department, Skopje, North Macedonia

September 2009 — October 2013

Graduated with thesis "Social Media Customer Relationship Management"

Achievements

UI/UX Hackathon - winning solution

August 2021

As part of a 48h hackathon, together with my team, I worked on a solution for a gamification tool for an e-learning platform - Brainobot, gaining first place. The solution is currently in development and will be distributed to real users.

Published conference paper: "UI Design Optimization and Analysis on Coupon Platforms for Improving Service Quality"

My master thesis was published as a conference paper at IEEE Xplore International Conference of Information Technologies.

ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8510727

Skills	Figma Miro	Adobe Creative Suite Trello
Languages	Macedonian Native speaker Serbian Native speaker	English Native speaker Czech A1
Links	<u>LinkedIn</u>	
Hobbies	Running, Cycling, Collecting Antiques	